in a shocking development conservative
air horn and thinking man Swamp Thing
Bill O'Reilly has been fired by
Fox big fans of that this comes amid
Revelations that the network paid out
multi-millions to settle multiple sexual
harassment suits involving the famously
Furious host when he's not aimlessly
shouting and harassing women who work
for him O'Reilly moonlights as the
bestselling author of Killing Lincoln
Killing Kennedy and killing
Reagan his next book will be killing my
own
career Bill's already transitioning from
the no Spin Zone to the no job Zone on
vacation today he was photographed
meeting the
pope guys guys I wonder if he had
anything to confess I don't know think
about it I mean listen if you get fired
for a raft of sexual harassment charges
you can always find a job in the
Catholic charge
heyo come on you
guys
hey comedians with the recent four years
of Catholic High School four years four
years Catholic High School with the
recent departures of O'Reilly and Megan
Kelly it seems like the conservative
news network is either trying to get rid
of every Irish person who works there or
undergoing major changes what is next
for Fox News Marcel I don't know Chris
but it'll definitely be racist as all
[Music]
right Chris they'll use all these
disasters to justify never hiring women
again because if they weren't around
none of this would have happened all
right Point that's their words not mine
yeah I like how you had to make the
clarification in that's that's not me
not I love my mama Russ russan uh
they're going to get George to come in
there and do The Fantastic Mr Fox News
oh that's fantastic well I wonder if
George Clooney were here right now what
he would say well I just did that a
there